<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue</string>
    <string-array name="data_title">
        <item>A Star Is Born</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avenger Invinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Creed 2</item>
        <item>Once Upon a Deadpool</item>
        <item>How To Train Your Dragon</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Hunter Killer</item>
        <item>Marry Popins</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers and falls in love with struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer — until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Allys career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</item>
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orms half-human, half Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock n roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercurys increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
        <item>Between personal obligations and training for his next big fight against an opponent with ties to his familys past, Adonis Creed is up against the challenge of his life.</item>
        <item>A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpools PG 13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride esque story thats full of magic, wonder and zero Fs.</item>
        <item>As the son of a Viking leader on the cusp of manhood, shy Hiccup Horrendous Haddock III faces a rite of passage: he must kill a dragon to prove his warrior mettle. But after downing a feared dragon, he realizes that he no longer wants to destroy it, and instead befriends the beast – which he names Toothless – much to the chagrin of his warrior father</item>
        <item>Trunks returns from the future to train with Goku and Vegeta. However, it disappears without warning. Then the mysterious Fu bursts in, telling them that Trunks has been imprisoned in the Prison Planet, a mysterious complex in an unknown place in the universes. The group seeks the dragon balls to free Trunks, but an endless battle awaits them! Will Goku and the others rescue Trunks and escape the Prison Planet?</item>
        <item>In a series of escalating encounters, security guard David Dunn uses his supernatural abilities to track Kevin Wendell Crumb, a disturbed man who has twenty-four personalities. Meanwhile, the shadowy presence of Elijah Price emerges as an orchestrator who holds secrets critical to both men.</item>
        <item>Captain Glass of the USS “Arkansas” discovers that a coup détat is taking place in Russia, so he and his crew join an elite group working on the ground to prevent a war.</item>
        <item>A magical nanny employs music and adventure to help two neglected children become closer to their father.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_image">
        <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_hunterkiller</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_marrypopins</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_release">
        <item>October 3, 2018</item>
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>April 27, 2018</item>
        <item>December 13, 2018</item>
        <item>November 2, 2018</item>
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>November 2, 2018</item>
        <item>December 13, 2018</item>
        <item>November 2, 2018</item>
        <item>May 10, 2018</item>
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>November 21, 2018</item>
        <item>May 10, 2018</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_score">
        <item>60</item>
        <item>68</item>
        <item>85</item>
        <item>88</item>
        <item>73</item>
        <item>66</item>
        <item>64</item>
        <item>80</item>
        <item>87</item>
        <item>88</item>
        <item>69</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>75</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
